<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RabbitA's Blog</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 04:55:54 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 04:55:54 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>iLotus主题更新</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haorooms.com/post/html_tsfh&quot;&gt;符号大全&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2014 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>/2014/01/04/iLotus.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2014/01/04/iLotus.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fantasy</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Don’t tell anyone this but I’m a fairy. Nobody knows you see because I never transform around other people. My name is Pixie and I am a green fairy. You see in the fairy tribe I come from they have three different types of fairies: the purple fairy, the green fairy and the yellow fairy. The purple fairies are the queen fairies the fairies that live inside the Queen fairies castle. The green fairies are just normal fairies and the yellow fairies are people such as nurse fairies etc…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am glad I am a green fairy because I get to do whatever I like and I have a really nice fairy house inside a giant mushroom. I usually transform at night when nobody is around. I started transforming into a fairy one day when I was about 9 and I think it was because I ate this crab apple and you’re not supposed to eat them! I am 11 now so that was 2 years ago. Now that I’m a fairy it gives me the ability to fly around which is great because at night I go to all my friends houses and check that they are okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes if they are having trouble getting to sleep or they are feeling ill or anything I use my magic to help them. The house I go to most often is Amie’s house because she’s my best friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are three different types of magic: the healing magic (that helps people), the touchstone magic (that makes things appear and disappear) and come along magic (that brings you anything you want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is my friend Ee-oor he is a little pocket dragon not like his cousins who are Wedge dragons (this means they are big and purple!) or like his other cousins who are minute dragons (this means they are almost invisible!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway I just thought you might like to know a few things about what it is like to be a fairy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>/2013/11/23/Fantasy.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2013/11/23/Fantasy.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My First Trip to Arizona</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;December 24, 1998
The plane ride to Arizona was fun.  The plane went very high and fast.  In the airport, I saw Uncle Jim, Grandpa, and Grandma.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We went to Grandpa and Grandma’s house.  Their house is pretty and they have a backyard.  I saw a dog in the backyard and Uncle Jim told me her name was B’Elena.   She flew on the airplane with Uncle Jim from Florida to Arizona.  I played with her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After lunch, I met Ruffy, a dog who lives near Grandma and Grandpa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I opened some presents at night and I had a Matchbox Car Airport in a big box. B’Elena knows how to open her presents by chewing them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;December 25, 1998
In the morning, Santa came to give our presents to us.  Grandma and Grandpa didn’t have any presents from Santa, but everybody had a stocking.  Santa gave me a painting set and model car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We ate lunch.  We passed out the bread and had ravioli and turkey with mashed potatoes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After we ate, we went outside and played.  My dad fixed my airport and I played with that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;December 26, 1998
When I was playing outside with my brother, Junior, and B’Elena, we saw a big balloon coming.  We drove to the store on the Indian reservation and we saw the big balloon in the park.  I walked up to the balloon and the man said he would give me a ride, but I didn’t want to go because it was so scary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That night, we went to Garcia’s for dinner.  After dinner, Grandpa and Grandma asked the waitress to bring hats with balloons on them and fried ice cream to the table for Junior and I.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At night, Grandpa brought his telescope out to the backyard.  I saw the moon, stars, Jupiter and Saturn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;December 27, 1998
B’Elena and Uncle Jim had to get on the airplane to go home from Arizona to Florida.   Florida is far away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We went to Casa Grande to see the Indian ruins.  We saw the walls, and we went in the rooms.  The walls and the rooms were pretty.  I walked through the mazes.   We saw a little door and everyone else was too big to walk through, but I could.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;December 28, 1998
We went to the Phoenix Zoo.  I saw zebras, giraffes, lions, tigers, cheetahs, rhinoceros and flamingos.  We rode a bus through the whole zoo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At night, we went back to the zoo to see ZooLights.  There were giraffes, lizards, monkeys, birds, and turtles made of lights.  There were trees that danced to the music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then we went to the Tumbleweed Tree.  It was very tall, and made of tumbleweed.   It had silver glitter and lights on it.  It had a big star on top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;December 29, 1998
We went to the Hall of Flame.  It is a big museum with fire trucks.  Some are new and some are old.  Grandpa was a fireman.  Grandpa told Junior and I to find the blue patch with an Indian on it.  He gave the museum that patch because that was from his fire company.  My dad, Junior, and I put on fire jackets and fire hats and Grandpa, Grandma and, my step-mom, Linda took a picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We went to Papago Park and Linda, Junior and I climbed up the mountain.   Then we waved to my dad, Grandpa and Grandma and then we went back.  My dad and I went up.   I climbed up the rocks and thought I was going to slide and fall down, then I climbed back down and we went to the other side of the mountain.  I almost fell and we held each other and I went down straight, but I didn’t run, I just walked.  Then we made it to the car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That night we went to Organ Stop Pizza.  We saw a man playing a large organ that moved.  When he finished, it went back down under the floor.  Then it came back up and he played again.  When he played, it was dark and then the ball went around and bubbles came out.  Then it stopped and the lights came back on.  There were flashing lights and cat puppets dancing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;December 30, 1998
We went to the Arizona Science Center.  At the fountain, I pressed a button and the water came over the fountain.  We saw a racing car.  I did an experiment with a color marker.  I drew a circle and the lady put water on it and the color moved on the paper.  We went into the Planetarium.  We saw Saturn, the moon, and Jupiter.   Then the man put up questions and we had to push buttons to give him the answer.   We went to see the movie “Super Speedway”.  It was about fixing a racing car.  The movie was very loud and the cars went very fast.  Then I dug in the rocks and moved them with a shovel.  I did more experiments.  We went out side and saw two big things (satellites)  that were very far apart.  Junior talked into one and I heard it through the other one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;December 31, 1998
Linda worked with me doing my letter books and my phonics book.  And after that Grandpa helped me play on the computer with my Jump Start Spelling and Numbers games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grandpa showed us antique gramophones.  They are old and play records.  You have to use the crank to turn them on.  The records sound like songs and talking.   They sound funny.  They belonged to Grandpa’s dad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That night Tyler, Kristine, and Ashley came over with their dad and mom for a New Year’s Eve party.  We played on the computer and we went to the park.  We played on the monkey bars.  Then I went on the swing.  Then Grandpa pushed me and Linda pushed Kristine.  I told Junior to move away please and I made a score with the basketball.   I painted wooden decorations with Kristine.  Then we colored felt decorations with markers and crayons.  At midnight we all said “Happy New Year” and gave hugs and kisses to each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;January 1, 1999
I put on Grandpa’s fire hat, fire jacket and fire boots.  The clothes were very heavy and the boots were big.  When I tried to walk I fell down and Grandpa and Junior had to help me up.  Everyone took pictures.  Junior, my dad, and Linda dressed up in the clothes too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tyler, Kristine, Ashley and their mom and dad came over for dinner.  We had lasagna and roast beef.  We went and played football in the backyard.  After that Julia came over with her mom, dad and brother.  We played on the computer.  We played with bubbles outside while our parents were talking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After everyone left, we went to say goodbye to Ruffy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;January 2, 1999
We all got up early and got dressed quickly.  We went to the airport.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We went back home on a very big airplane.  On the airplane I sat with Linda and my dad.  Dad was in the middle and I was by the window so I could see everything.   Junior was behind us.  I played and went to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we got home, it was very cold.  We all had to hold suitcases on the way home because we brought back so much stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought the vacation was very nice.  I liked it because Arizona is very fun.   My favorite things to do in Arizona were going to the zoo, Zoolights and the Indian ruins.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2012 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>/2012/12/22/TheFirstTrip.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2012/12/22/TheFirstTrip.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>markdown</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Markdown is a lightweight markup language with plain text formatting syntax designed so that it can be converted to HTML and many other formats using a tool by the same name. Markdown is often used to format readme files, for writing messages in online discussion forums, and to create rich text using a plain text editor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key design goal is readability – that the language be readable as-is, without looking like it has been marked up with tags or formatting instructions, unlike text formatted with a markup language, such as Rich Text Format (RTF) or HTML, which have obvious tags and formatting instructions. To this end, its main inspiration is the existing conventions for marking up plain text in email, though it also draws from earlier markup languages, notably setext, Textile, and reStructuredText.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gruber wrote a Perl script, Markdown.pl, which converts marked-up text input to valid, well-formed XHTML or HTML and replaces left-pointing angle brackets ‘&amp;lt;’ and ampersands ‘&amp;amp;’ with their corresponding character entity references. It can be used as a standalone script, as a plugin for Blosxom or Movable Type, or as a text filter for BBEdit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Markdown has since been re-implemented by others as a Perl module available on CPAN (Text::Markdown), and in a variety of other programming languages.It is distributed under a BSD-style license and is included with, or available as a plugin for, several content-management systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sites such as GitHub, reddit, Diaspora, Stack Exchange, OpenStreetMap, and SourceForge use variants of Markdown to facilitate discussion between users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Standardization[edit]
There is no clearly defined Markdown standard, apart from the original writeup and implementation by John Gruber, which some consider abandonware. This has led to fragmentation as different vendors write their own variants of the language to correct flaws or add missing features.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A number of other lightweight markup languages extend Markdown by adding features (such as tables, footnotes, definition lists, and Markdown inside HTML blocks) not available in original Markdown syntax. Among these are Markdown Extra, MultiMarkdown, and the Pandoc Markdown extension.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The original Markdown implementation interprets constructs like my_long_variable as a request to emphasize “long”. Many users found this confusing, so many later implementations such as PHP Markdown and Python Markdown do not implement middle word emphasis with underscores.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Babelmark2 is a tool available to “[compare] the output of various implementations” to “promote discussion of how and whether certain vague aspects of the markdown spec should be clarified.” Gruber has argued that complete standardisation would be mistaken: “Different sites (and people) have different needs. No one syntax would make all happy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In March 2016 RFC 7763 and RFC 7764 were published. RFC 7763 introduced MIME type text/markdown with the original variant. RFC 7764 discusses and registered the variants MultiMarkdown, GFM, Pandoc, CommonMark, and Markdown Extra among others.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>/2011/12/02/markdown.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2011/12/02/markdown.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>GitHub</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The shading of the map illustrates the number of users as a proportion of each country’s Internet population. The circular charts surrounding the two hemispheres depict the total number of GitHub users (left) and commits (right) per country.
24 February 2009: GitHub team members announced, in a talk at Yahoo! headquarters, that within the first year of being online, GitHub had accumulated over 46,000 public repositories, 17,000 of which were formed in the previous month alone. At that time, about 6,200 repositories had been forked at least once and 4,600 had been merged.
5 July 2009: GitHub announced that the site was now harnessed by over 100,000 users.
27 July 2009: In another talk delivered at Yahoo!, Tom Preston-Werner announced that GitHub had grown to host 90,000 unique public repositories, 12,000 having been forked at least once, for a total of 135,000 repositories.[21]
25 July 2010: GitHub announced that it hosts 1 million repositories.[22]
20 April 2011: GitHub announced that it is hosting 2 million repositories.[23]
2 June 2011: ReadWriteWeb reported that GitHub had surpassed SourceForge and Google Code in total number of commits for the period January to May 2011.[24]
9 July 2012: Peter Levine, general partner at GitHub’s investor Andreessen Horowitz, stated that GitHub had been growing revenue at 300% annually since 2008 “profitably nearly the entire way”.[25]
16 January 2013: GitHub announced it had passed the 3 million users mark and was then hosting more than 5 million repositories.[26]
23 December 2013: GitHub announced it had reached 10 million repositories.[27]
In June 2015, GitHub opened an office in Japan that is its first office outside of the U.S.[28]
29 July 2015: GitHub announced it had raised $250 million in funding in a round led by Sequoia Capital. The round valued the company at approximately $2 billion.[29]
这个 violet 主题已经用了 2 年。今天一气之下将其改头换面，这个皮肤你喜欢么？恩，随便下载使用。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;section&quot;&gt;为什么我要换个地方写博客呢？&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;原因很多，有一个原因是因为这里的文章，被 fork 之后，就成为别人的文章。很多没删的，就这样复制过去自己的博客了。不是很喜欢。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;另外，我喜欢不同的尝试，恩，爱折腾呗。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;pizn-&quot;&gt;PIZn 换到「掌心」&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;有一句老话，前端的博客，更换主题比更换文章来的多。好像是的，我就是这样的一个博客，平时也就练练写代码，搞设计的那种感觉。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;后来，就不是这样了，学习到的内容需要有个地方可以沉淀，于是换了个域名，改变了写作方式。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;欢迎访问&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.zhanxin.info&quot;&gt;「掌心」&lt;/a&gt;，这里是我的新窝。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2010 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>/2010/11/23/GitHub.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2010/11/23/GitHub.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
